clinch.co 2016-02-15

# Clinch - Privacy policy

**Clinch – Programmatic Creative**

**_Privacy Policy_**

At Clinch Labs we take your privacy very seriously. The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain the principles of our ‘Programmatic Creative’ advertising solution and the data that it collects from our ads viewers ("you").

Clinch Labs reserves the right, at our discretion, to change this privacy policy at any time. Changes will be effective 10 days following posting of the revised privacy policy on our website. Your continued use of our website 10 days following such posting means you are accepting those changes.  

**About Clinch Programmatic Creative**

Clinch Labs specializes in automated generation of dynamic HTML5 rich media advertising across all devices. Our platform is transforming clients online shopping experience and improving communication between a brand and its audience through innovative, engaging ads. These ads result higher conversion rates and ROI to our clients. Our objective is to provide, best optimize and personalized dynamic rich media ads to customers of our clients across the web. 

Clinch Labs strongly believes that in a fast paced world, consumers like to receive personalized and tailored ads that display updated and relevant content to their specific needs across all their devices. They want to interact with it and explore more exciting content. Therefore by turning online catalogs and structured webpages into dynamic ads, our clients’ audiences are, as we’ve seen, significantly more likely to engage and convert via our unique ads.

**What information does Clinch Programmatic Creative collect?**

Clinch Labs, with its Programmatic Creative platform, _does not_ collect any personal information that can be used to identify you. Personal information refers to any information that may be used, either as-is or combined with other information, to identify an individual, such as, but not limited to, a first and last name, personal profile, physical address, an email address or other contact information. In cases when data is collected, it is completely anonymous and includes information, which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as the Internet Browser you are using to access websites, whether you have visited our clients’ websites, and random collected data about how our clients’ websites and services are being used. The information Clinch Labs might be aware of is that a certain user (No personal information included - name, address, email, etc.) visited several products pages recently and this information is used to present videos and ads that are relevant to those products.

**How is this anonymous information collected?**

Clinch Labs may choose to collect the anonymous information through the use of browser cookies and/or via user interaction or engagement with our ads (viewing ad impressions or clicking the ad). Browser cookies record, for example, the pages you browsed on our clients' websites. When you visit our clients’ websites that Clinch Programmatic Creative is integrated with, your browser sends the anonymous cookie and based on the information stored there, you should receive better-targeted and relevant ads than the standard you would receive without using Clinch Programmatic Creative. Clinch Labs has no way, need or desire to identify you throughout this process.

You can remove our cookies and opt-out by clicking the following link: **_[Here](http://clinch.co/opt-out.html)_**

You can opt-in again in order to receive a better targeted and personalized ad experience by clicking **_[Here](http://clinch.co/opt-in.html)_**

**Display of Clinch Programmatic Creative Ads.**

Clinch Labs’ Programmatic Creative ads run on many Internet websites and mobile applications as part of their promotion, advertising and video programming. The ads could appear in relevant product pages, as stand-alone ads, social media posts or ads, banners and before or during the playback of a video that you chose to watch. Many of these publishers access Clinch Labs through third-party advertising networks or ad exchanges. Those networks may also place cookies on your browser upon visiting a Clinch customer’s website to facilitate ad serving as described above. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). In addition, you can opt out of any other third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.

**Links & Third-Party Sites**

Clinch may choose to implement and incorporate, as part of the assets in its ad creation, specific content from its clients databases, Third party services Clinch Labs’ clients are using as well as Google services such as: Google Maps / Earth / Places APIs. Therefore by using Clinch application, clients and users acknowledge and agree to be bound by Clinch Labs’ clients Privacy Policy and [_Google Privacy Policy_](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy) _._

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our policies, please [contact us](http://www.clinch.co/) through our website. Alternatively you can contact us in writing at the following address. We will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

**Clinch Labs**

56 Hakochavim st. Caesarea, Israel 30889.

Last revised: Mar. 29th 2015.
